<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<channel><item><title>Chief Engineer</title><ref>Job 9719 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Y3
Chief Engineer experience on similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean / Caribbean</Location><Job_Description>A  35M+ Charter M/Y  are looking for a hands on  Relief  Chief Engineer  to join their team  by the 10th March for approximately 2 weeks!  The ideal candidate will have a  3+ years  in a  similar role  aboard  Yachts.  Candidates will need to be 'hands on' in this role and have a 'can do' attitude. Candidates will also need to be fluent in the English language. The minimum certification needed would be: STCW Basic Training, Security Awareness, Seafarer Medical and a Minimum Licence  2 nd  Engineer (MN) III/3 or 2 nd  Engineer (Yacht Y3)  with Engine Manufacturer Course Yacht (MTU 4000s). Salary will be paid in Euros and DOE.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Mate/Engineer</title><ref>Job 9716 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Temporary</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>MEOL
Prior yachting experience.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  experienced 2nd Mate / Engineer  is required to join a  50M+ yacht  on a  temporary basis  within the  next few days. Applicants must have  previous yachting experience  working in a similar role and should be competent in all  Deck and Engine tasks. The certificates required would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical and a MEOL Licence,  along with a  suitable Deck Qualification. On offer is a  Temporary contract  and  Day rate Euro Salary. Those already in Europe / MED will be considered first.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Second Stewardess</title><ref>Job 9713 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>1.5+ years longevity</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  Experienced 2nd Stewardess  is required to join a  50M+ Sailing Yacht ASAP. Applicants must have  1+ years previous experience  working as  2nd Stewardess and 1.5 years longevity  on the same yacht. Additional skills such as  cooking  would be an advantage but not essential. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic training, and ENG1 Medical. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  45 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess (yacht)</title><ref>Job 9711 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Temporary</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>previous experience in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>A  Stewardess  is required to join a  50M+ Yacht,  Immediately Applicants will require  1+ years previous experience  working as  Stewardess aboard similar sized yachts. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training and a ENG1 Medical. Salary TBC and Seasonal Contract.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Galley Hand / Steward/ess</title><ref>Job 9709 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>previous experience in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>A  Galley Steward  is needed to join a  100M+ Private M/Y ASAP. The ideal candidate will  have 1-2 years experience  in a  similar role aboard large yachts or luxury cruise ships. Applicants will need to be able to  prepare food and maintain cleanliness and hygiene standards. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW basic training, Security Awareness, Passenger safety certificate  and a  Food &amp; Hygiene level 2 On offer is a  Euro salary,   and leave package. Male candidates only due to cabin arrangements.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Nurse</title><ref>Job 9708 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>2+ years in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Other (see notes)</Location><Job_Description>A  Nurse/Housekeeping Stewardess  is required to join a  100m+ M/Y ASAP . We are looking for a team player, and a level headed Nurse with emergency experience. Ideal applicants will also have a couple of years experience working on large yachts and have good knowledge working in all aspects of the interior - housekeeping experience a must.  Certification required: STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Security Awareness, Level 2 Food and Hygiene and relevant Nursing qualification.  To begin ASAP - Euro salary and 91 days leave per year. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Second Stewardess</title><ref>Job 9701 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Temporary</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>At least 1 year experience on yachts this size</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>We are looking for a  Seasonal  Second  Stewardess  to join a  40m + yacht ASAP. At least 1 years experience in this rank   aboard  similar sized yachts  is essential along with cooking skills.  The minimum certification needed would be  STCW Basic Training  and an  ENG1 Medical. On offer is an industry standard  Euro salary  as well as  36 days leave per year  and a Seasonal contract. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess (yacht)</title><ref>Job 9690 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Previous high end hospitality experience.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  experienced Service Stewardess  is needed to join  100M+ M/Y ASAP. Applicants must have a  background in High end hospitality  as well as  previous experience  in a similar role  aboard large yachts  and should be  skilled and experienced  with all  Service Styles. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training  and a  ENG1 Medical. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  5 months on 1 Month off rotation.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Housekeeping Stewardess</title><ref>Job 9686 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>one year + on 80m+ yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>A  Housekeeping Stewardess  is needed to join a  100m+  private motor yacht in  April . At least one years experience on 80m+ yachts preferred. Must have good overall knowledge of yacht cleaning procedures and detailing, and hands on experience with 'beds &amp; heads'. Candidates who prefer to remain in housekeeping will be considered first.  Certification required: STCW, PDSD, ENG1, Food &amp; Hygiene Level 2 and B1/B2 visa.  Female  only due to cabin arrangements on-board.  USD salary and 5:1 leave package on offer. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess</title><ref>Job 9685 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>experience on yachts over 80m preferred</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>A  Service Stewardess  is required to join a  100m+  private motor yacht in  April .  Experience on yachts over 80m preferred. Must have good foundation knowledge in food and beverage and a genuine passion for food, drink and hospitality.  Certification required: STCW, PDSD, ENG1, Food &amp; Hygiene Level 2 and B1/B2 visa.  Female  only due to cabin arrangements on-board.  USD salary and 3:1 leave package on offer. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Deckhand</title><ref>Job 9682 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>1-2 years experience in a similar role.</Certification_Experience><Location>Middle East</Location><Job_Description>A hard working and motivated  Deckhand  is needed to join a  100m+ Private Yacht  by  early March 2018. Applicants must  1-2 years experience  as a Deckhand on  larger yachts  and should be well versed in all  general deck maintenance  and  tender driving tasks. The minimum certification required would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Security Awareness  and a  Power Boat Level 2 certificate.  A B1 B2 Visa is ideally required, but there is time to obtain one for the right candidate. Males need only apply due to cabin arrangements.  On offer is a  Euro Salary, 3 months on 1 Month off  and  Medical insurance.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Chef de partie</title><ref>Job 9681 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Worldwide</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>A  Chef De Partie  is needed to join a  100M+ Support Vesse l in the begining of  March. The ideal candidate will have  1+ years  in a  similar role aboard large yachts  and / or  cruise ships.  Applicants will be assisting with  food preparation  as well as the maintaining the high standards and cleanliness of the galley. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Security awareness, Passenger Safety Certificate, Food and Hygiene Level 2  and a  appropriate cook / chef certificate. On offer is a  Euro salary, 122 days leave per year  and a  flight package. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess</title><ref>Job 9680 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>At least one season’s experience on a yacht or cruise ship which includes Stewarding</Certification_Experience><Location>Other (see notes)</Location><Job_Description>A  Stewardess  is required to join a  60m+ M/Y  on the  1st of March .  We are looking for a confident team player, and applicants must have  at least one season's experience  on a yacht or cruise ship which includes Housekeeping and/or Stewarding.  Minimum certification needed is:  STCW, Security Awareness, Seafarer Medical.  Female  only due to cabin arrangements on-board.  Euro  salary,  122 leave days  and  2 return flights  per year. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Hairdresser</title><ref>Job 9675 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>At least 1 year experience on yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>We have a fantastic opportunity for a  Hairdresser/Stewardess  to join an 80m+ Motor Yacht in April 2018. Candidates must be a  professionally trained  Hairdresser, and previous yachting experience is preferred. Valid  STCW and ENG1  essential. Females need only apply due to cabin arrangements. Salary in  Euros .  5 months on, 1 month off . 2 return flights per year.   Apply today if you would like to be considered.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Technical Manager</title><ref>Job 9674 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Chief engineer unlimited
Previous experience as a Naval Architect and/or Chief Engineer/2nd Engineer</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>We are looking for  Technical Managers  to join a  yacht management company  based in the Med to provide technical support to the company and crew onboard.  Applicants will require a Degree in Naval Architecture, Marine Engineering or Project Management . Previous experience as a Naval Architect and/or Chief Engineer/2nd Engineer. Position will involve frequent travel in order to carry out technial inspections onboard. You will also be responsible for securing refit projects and overseeing ship yard periods and working closely wiht suppliers and contractors. Package details to be discussed at interview stages.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Second Stewardess</title><ref>Job 9668 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>At least 2.5 years experience on yachts 60m+</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>A well presented  Senior Stewardess  is required to join a 90m+  M/Y by April 2018.  Start date is flexible for the right candidate.  Previous proven longevity is essential along with at least  3 years experience  in similar roles on yachts 60m+. Candidates must also be passionate about the yachting industry, be able to demonstrate the ability to function effectively in a high-pressure environment and will be positive, energetic and methodical individuals.  The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training,   ENG1 Medical,  Proficiency in Designated Security Duties and Level 2 Food, Safety &amp; Hygiene.  On offer is a competitive  Euro Salary  and an approx rotation of 21 weeks ON / 5 weeks OFF. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess (yacht)</title><ref>Job 9667 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>1+ years experience in a similar role aboard large yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>A number of  Junior Stewardesses  are required to join a  90M+ M/Y by April 2018. Applicants will require 1+ years experience working aboard a  50M+ yacht  in the role of  Stewardess . Experience in both  Housekeeping and Service  would be required. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, DSD, ENG1 Medical, Level 2 Food and Hygiene  and ideally a  B1 B2 Visa. On offer is a  Euro Salary and Rotational based leave package. Yacht is currently in the MED, with a worldwide itinerary.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Sous chef</title><ref>Job 9662 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>3 years+</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>An  experienced Sous Chef  is needed to join a  100M+ M/Y   ASAP. The ideal candidate will have  previous experience  in a  similar role aboard large private yachts or cruise ships  and have good knowledge and skills in a wide range of cuisines.  You will be leading a team of 4 CdP and 3 messmen, The minimum certification needed is:   STCW Basic Training  and an  ENG1 Medical. On offer is a  USD Salary  and a  6 Months on 2 Months off rotation.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Chief Steward/ess (Yacht)</title><ref>Job 9660 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>2+ years in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Middle East</Location><Job_Description>An  organised Chief Stewardess  is required to join a  65M+ Private yacht  in the  Middle East, ASAP. Applicants will required  2+ years prior yachting  experience working as  Chief Stewardess  aboard similar  sized yachts. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and  security awareness  (or higher.) On offer is a  Salary paid in AED  and  30 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Sous chef</title><ref>Job 9656 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Familiar Italian, French, Mediterranean, Chinese and Kosher cuisine</Certification_Experience><Location>Far East</Location><Job_Description>An  experienced 2nd Chef  is required to join a  95M+ Yacht ASAP,  in the Far east. Applicants must have  2-5 years  proven experience working as a  2nd Chef , including  1+ year  working aboard a  large yacht.  Knowledge of a range of Cuisines such as  Italian, French, Mediterranean, Chinese and Kosher  would be required. Pastry skills would be useful. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Food and Hygiene level 2, Ships Cook Certificate, Security Awareness, Crowd Management  and a  B1 B2 Visa. On offer is a  Euro salary  and  4 Months on 2 Months off rotation  and  shared cabin.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Deckhand</title><ref>Job 9641 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>1+ years in a similar role aboard large yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An experienced  Deckhand  is required to join a  50M+ M/Y ASAP. Applicants will required  1+ years prior experience  working as  Deckhand  aboard  similar sized yachts. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training  and  ENG1 Medical. Salary / package TBC</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Nurse</title><ref>Job 9634 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>one season working aboard Cruise ships or yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>A  Nurse / Stewardess  is needed to join a  100M+ M/Y  in  March 2018. Applicants will need at least  one seasons  experience aboard a  Cruise ship or large yacht  and should have an e xtensive A&amp;E / Paramedic  or  Medical Officer background. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Security Awareness  and A  Registered Nursing certificate / Degree.  On offer is a  Euro Salary and 122 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Chief Steward/ess (Yacht)</title><ref>Job 9629 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>5+ Years experience in similar roles.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  organised Chief Stewardess  is needed to join a  100M+ New build  in the  MED  from  April 2018. Applicants must have  5+ years maritime experience  working aboard  similar sized yachts / cruise ships  and should have  excellent Crew Organisation and management skills. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Passenger Safety Certificate, Security Awareness  and the  legal right to work in Europe. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  good package.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Head chef</title><ref>Job 9628 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>4 years + Fine Dinning</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>Viking are looking for a  Sole Chef   (male only due to cabin arrangement) to join a  50m M/Y  that is currently based   in the  Mediterranean  for a late March start date . The vessel is both  Private &amp; Charter,  and you will be cooking for  11 crew, as well as up to 10 charter guests  at times.   Candidates will have successfully worked on a yacht of this size before as a Sole Chef, with proven longevity and have  references to match.   Ideally candidates will also have prior experience in  Fine Dinning,  and be will comfortable plating to a high-standard, as well as provisioning.    The up-coming summer is going to be very busy with both owner and charter trips, so candidates will need to be organised and top of their game. Candidates will hold an STCW &amp; ENG1  as well as a  certificate or diploma in cookery  from a professional provider (a Ships Cook Certificate would also be considered), and a Level 2 Food &amp; Hygiene Certificate. Competitive salary paid in Euros.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Deckhand</title><ref>Job 9623 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Navigational Watch Rating
2+ years in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  experienced Deckhand  is needed to join a  100M+ M/Y ASAP  in the  MED. Applicants will need to have  2+ years previous experience  in a  previous role serving as Deckhand  aboard  large Yachts/Passenger ships. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Security Awareness, Passenger Safety Certificate  and  Navigational Watch Rating.  Additional certificates such as Power Boat Level 2, Personal Watercraft and Helicopter Landing Officer. On offer is a Euro Salary, 122 days leave per year  and  flight package.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Bosun</title><ref>Job 9607 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Navigational Watch Rating
2 years yachting and Navigational Watch Rating licence</Certification_Experience><Location>Middle East</Location><Job_Description>An  experienced Bosun  is needed to join a  80M+ Private Yacht ASAP. Applicants will need  2+ years experience  working on yachts including  experience as Bosun. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and  Navigational watch. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  45 days leave per year. Yacht is currently based in the Middle East.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Head chef</title><ref>Job 9603 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>3 years on vessels</Certification_Experience><Location>Middle East</Location><Job_Description>Viking are looking for a Head Chef to join a 40m+ (motor) catamaran that is permanently based in UAE waters. The position is based on a Sun-Thurs 8am to 5pm workday and the Head Chef will also be standing by for any upcoming trips.  You will be working with a Sous and 3rd Chef - and will need to be competent leading and teaching the galley team, while producing a high level of food for the guests on board as well as 2 meals a day for the crew (lunch and dinner).  This would be best suited to a person who wants to relocate to the UAE for a few years and is happy with the 30 days leave on offer. The salary is generous for a vessel of this size, although the candidate will also need to find land based accommodation close by (help will be given with this).  Medical, a mobile phone allowance and one return flight to country of origin is included in the package also.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Masseuse</title><ref>Job 9601 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Masseuse with Accounting knowledge.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean / Caribbean</Location><Job_Description>A  Chief Stewardess/Interior Manager  with  massage qualifications  is needed to join a  60M+ Private Yacht ASAP. Applicants will need an  extensive Masseuse  background, serving aboard similar sized yachts. Candidates should also have prior  Accounting knowledge / skills and experience of leading a team. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training  and a  ENG1 Medical.  A B1 B2 Visa, Accounting qualification and Masseuse Qualification would be ideal. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  60 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Deckhand / Water Sports Instructor</title><ref>Job 9599 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Temporary</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Extensive Jet Ski background.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  Energetic Stand-Up Jetski instructor / Deckhand  is required to join a  45M+ private Yacht  from  April. Applicants will need an  extensive background   driving and instructing  on  STAND-UP   Jet Skis   and should be confident in  Jet Ski  maintenance.  Some yachting experience would be useful, however for those with the background above this is not essential. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and relevant  JetSki Certifications. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  Seasonal Contract. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Chief Steward/ess (Yacht)</title><ref>Job 9578 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>4+ years in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  organised Chief Stewardess  is needed to join a  45M+ Charter S/Y ASAP. Applicants will require  4+ years experience  in a similar role, including  2+ years  aboard the same yacht. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training  and a  ENG1 Medical. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  60 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>2nd Engineer</title><ref>Job 9577 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Y4
2+ years in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An experienced  2nd Engineer  is required to join a  50M+ Charter Sailing Yacht ASAP.   1+ year longevity  engineering experience aboard a yacht would be required and  ideally some previous CAT engine  experience. Additional skills such as  Water Sports and Tender Driving  would also be needed.  Looking for someone that could step up to Chief Engineer in the next year. The minimum certification would be  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical and an MEOL licence or better.  On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  45 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Second Stewardess</title><ref>Job 9571 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>previous experience in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean / Caribbean</Location><Job_Description>An organised  Senior Service Stewardess  is required to join a  100M+ M/Y ASAP. Applicants will require  Previous longevity  in a  similar role aboard a large yacht  and the ability to  lead the Service team effectively.  The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training  and a  ENG1 Medical. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  3 Months on 1 Month off rotation.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Chief Engineer</title><ref>Job 9570 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Y4
previous experience in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Caribbean</Location><Job_Description>A  Reliable Engineer  is needed to join a  30M+ Private Yacht ASAP  in the  Caribbean. Applicants must have  previous experience  working in a  similar role  and  ideally Caterpillar Engine experience.  The  successful candidate  will also be assisting with mooring operations and tenders. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and a  Y4 / Y3 licence. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  38 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Chief Steward/ess (Yacht)</title><ref>Job 9567 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Previous Yard or New build experience</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An experienced  Chief Stewardess  is required to join a New Build 90M+ in February/March. Applicants must have prior experience working as Chief Stewardess aboard a New build or whilst in a Yard Period. Applicants need to have American style cuisine and dining experience as well as fine European dining experience. Must also be able to interact with the guests at a very professional level and manage a team of 10.  The minimum certification needed would be: STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical,  recognised Wine Course  and Cocktail/bar course. Apply now, if you meet all the above requirements!</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess (yacht)</title><ref>Job 9566 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>2+ years in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An Outgoing &amp; confident  3rd Stewardess  is needed in the  MED  to join a  private 40M+ Yacht ASAP. Applicants must have  1+ Season prior experience  working in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts. Bartending or Wine Service skills will be highly advantageous. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and a  Food &amp; Hygiene Level 2 Certificate. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  42 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Second Stewardess</title><ref>Job 9565 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>3+ years experience in a similar role.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  Organised  and  outgoing  2nd Stewardess  is required to join a  40M+ Private Yacht  in the  MED, ASAP. Applicants will require 2 + years experience  in a similar role aboard  30M+ yachts.  Applicants should also have  bar tending  and  Wine Service Skills. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and  Food and Hygiene Certificate. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  42 Days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Deckhand</title><ref>Job 9564 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>2+ Seasons in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>An  Ambitious Deckhand  is needed to join a  40M+ Yacht  in the  MED ASAP. Applicants will required  1+ Seasons  in a similar role aboard  similar sized yachts, Excellent Tender driving skills  and great all round  painting and varnishing knowledge. The minimum certification required would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and a   Personal Water Craft certificate. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  42 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Bosun</title><ref>Job 9563 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Yachtmaster offshore
4+ seasons experience in a similar role aboard large yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>A  Reliable Bosun  is required to join a  40M+ Private Yacht ASAP. Applicants should have at least  4+ years experience  in a  similar role  and should have prior  experience leading the Deck team  and  painting and varnishing skills. The minimum certificate needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, PWC Licence  and a  Yachtmaster Offshore licence. On offer is a good  Euro Salary  and  42 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Masseuse</title><ref>Job 9551 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>previous experience in a similar role.</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean</Location><Job_Description>We are looking for an ambitious  Stewardess / Masseuse / Beautician  to join a  100M+ Yacht.  Applicants should have an extensive  Masseuse / Beautician  background aboard  Cruise ships / Yachts or at high end hospitality establishments.  Additional skills such as Hairdressing would be useful. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training  and a  ENG1 Medical. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  5/1 rotation.  Start date is flexible, within the next few weeks. </Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Beauty Therapist</title><ref>Job 9539 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>6+ months experience aboard large yachts.</Certification_Experience><Location>Far East</Location><Job_Description>A  Beautician  / Hairdresser   is required to join a  100M+ Support vessel ASAP. Applicants will need a  background  working aboard a  Large yacht  in a  similar role.  Experience in a range of  Beauty Treatments  and  Hair styling  would be essential. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and relevant Masseuse qualifications. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  122 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Masseuse</title><ref>Job 9538 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>60M+ yacht experience in a similar role.</Certification_Experience><Location>Far East</Location><Job_Description>A  Masseuse / Stewardess  is required to join a  100M+ Support vessel ASAP. Applicants will need a  background  working aboard a  Large yacht  in a  similar role.  Experience in a range of  Massage techniques and therapies  would be essential. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical  and relevant Masseuse qualifications. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  122 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess (yacht)</title><ref>Job 9536 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>3+ seasons experience in a similar role aboard large yachts or cruise ships.</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>A Number of  Aspiring Service Stewardesses  are required to join a  100M+ support vessel  in  February 2018. Applicants will require  3+ seasons experience  aboard  large yachts / cruise ships  and should have  excellent Service skills. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical Security Awareness,  and a  Passenger Safety Certificate. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  122 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Hotel engineer</title><ref>Job 9519 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Engine Room Watch Rating
previous experience in a similar role.</Certification_Experience><Location>Northern Europe</Location><Job_Description>An  experienced Assistant Hotel Engineer  is required to join a  New build 100M+ in February. Applicant will need previous experience in similar roles aboard  large yachts / Cruise ships,  New build experience would be useful but not essential.  Good Knowledge of delicate materials  such as Marbles, Wood Veneers, carpet and leather would be needed, as wood an excellent understanding of  Engine room systems. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training, ENG1 Medical, Engine Room Watch Keeping Certification  and the required documentation to work in Europe for the duration of the contract. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  Land Based contract  (based on 5 day work week with 30 days leave,)  accommodation  and  health insurance.  After Build the contract would switch to a Seagoing one on Full rotation.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Deckhand</title><ref>Job 9492 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Navigational Watch Rating
2+ years in a similar role aboard similar sized yachts</Certification_Experience><Location>Mediterranean / Caribbean</Location><Job_Description>A  Dedicated Deckhand  is required to join a  100M+ Private Yacht ASAP. Applicants will need  2+ years  experience working as  Deckhand aboard similarly sized vessels.  Applicants should have experience in all  exterior maintenance  including  painting, varnishing, paint stripping, waxing and various products.  Experience  maintaining various water toys, line handling and fishing gear knowledge  would be useful. The minimum certification needed would be:  STCW Basic Training ,  ENG1 Medical  and a  Navigational Watch Rating Certificate. On offer is a  Euro Salary  and  122 days leave per year.</Job_Description></description></item><item><title>Steward/ess</title><ref>Job 9491 </ref><description><Employer_Type>Yacht</Employer_Type><Job_Type>Permanent</Job_Type><Certification_Experience>Highly experienced hospitality professional</Certification_Experience><Location>Worldwide</Location><Job_Description>An 80m+ Private Motor Yacht are looking for an experienced Service Stewardess to join their team in April.  Must have a minimum of 2 years experience in a similar role on yachts over 70m. A strong service background with extensive bar-tending and beverage skills is a must. Confidence with the following skills: Silver service, barista and bar-tending, experience with stock control, and intermediate to advanced computer skills.  Valid STCW, PDSD, Seafarers medical, and B1/B2 visa required.  60 days vacation per year, salary paid in USD. </Job_Description></description></item></channel>